（忆往昔）
我不相信
I don't believe it.
怀俄明州 什么意思
Wyoming? What does it mean?
图上每一个叉都是一个废弃的边境教堂
Each of these x's is an abandoned frontier church …
都是十九世纪中期
all mid-19th century,
由萨穆埃尔·科尔特建造
built by Samuel Colt.
萨穆埃尔·科尔特
Samuel Colt …
那个能杀恶魔
The demon-killing,
- 又会做枪的萨穆埃尔·科尔特吗 - 是
- gunmaking Samuel Colt? - Yep.
他建造了连接教堂的私人铁路
He built private railway lines connecting church to church.
连起来恰好是这个图形
It just happens to lay out like this.
这是个恶魔陷阱
It's a devil's trap.
一个一百平方英里的恶魔陷阱
A 100-square-mile devil's trap.
1973年
1973.
- 怎么回事 - 看起来像怎么回事
- What is this? - What does it look like?
- 这是真的吗 - 非常真
- Is it real? - Very.
好吧 怎么着 天使操纵了时间机器吗
Okay, so, what, angels got their hands on some Deloreans?
我怎么到这的
How did I get here?
时间是流动的 迪恩
Time is fluid, Dean.
这不容易 但我们偶尔能扭曲时间
It's not easy, but we can bend it on occasion.
我在想你们该知道「炼狱」
But I'm thinking you know "Purgatory."
一切都是为了打开一扇门让什么东西进来
This is all about opening a door to let something in.
- 什么东西 - 我正在研究
- What? - I'm working on it.
- 能给点提示吗 - 查到个名字
- Could you give us something? - I got a name.
「万物之母」
"Mother of all."
我们都不知道怎样猎杀她
We got zero on ganking her.
我们有很多事要做 开始吧
We have so much to do. Let's get started.
她有话告诉你们
She has a message for you.
是吗 什么
Oh, yeah? What's that?
你们都会死
You're all gonna die.
（如今）
（怀俄明州 桑赖斯 1861年3月5日）
[邪恶力量 第6季第18集]
（48小时前）
就在这里某个地方 我确定
It's here, somewhere. I know it.
帮我搬开这个
Help me move this.
我嘞个去
I'll be damned.
欢迎来到坎贝尔家族图书馆
Welcome to the Campbell family library.
这些东西都是萨穆埃尔收集的喽
So, Samuel collected all this stuff, huh?
明显是的
Apparently.
哇
Wow.
好吧 我们要找什么
All right, well, what are we looking for?
任何能打跑万物之母的东西
Well, anything that'll put a run in the octomom's stockings.
选一排吧
Pick a row.
找到了
Bingo.
你们两个家伙有没有
Either of you jokers ever heard.
听说过有关凤凰的事
anything about a phoenix?
瑞弗（美国影星） 华金（美国歌手） 还是巨大的火鸟
River, Joaquin, or the giant flaming bird?
这上面说
It says here.
凤凰的灰烬可以烧毁万物之母
that the ashes of a phoenix can burn the mother.
万物之母
The mother?
好 我们上哪能弄到一个
Great. Where do we get one?
你问住我了 我还以为那是个神话
You got me. I thought it was a myth.
好吧
All right, great.
看看咱能不能找到关于凤凰的资料
Well, let's see if we can find something out about a phoenix.
伙计们
Guys.
伙计们 伙计们 伙计们
Guys, guys, guys, guys, guys,
听听这个
Check this out.
1861年3月5日
"March 5, 1861.
桑赖斯 怀俄明州
Sunrise, Wyoming.
今天枪杀了一只凤凰
Gun killed a phoenix today.
留下了一堆阴燃的灰烬
Left a pile of smoldering ash."
真的假的 谁的枪
Really? Whose gun?
科尔特的
CoIt's.
科尔特 就是那个科尔特
Colt? Colt like …
就是那个科尔特
Like the Colt.
来自
From…
萨穆埃尔·科尔特的日记
…Samuel CoIt's… journal.
什么
What?!
- 这是他的吗 - 对
- That's his? - Yeah.
- 老哥 不是吧 - 老弟 是的
- Dude, no. - Dude, yes.
- 让我看看 - 才不给你
- Well, let me see it. - Get your own.
关于凤凰他还说什么了
Well, what else did he say about the phoenix?
它长什么样 有羽毛吗
What does it look like? Has it got feathers?
上面只写了「凤凰」
It just says "Phoenix."
- 他说了在哪找到的吗 - 没有
- Did he say where he tracked it? - No.
好了 我想咱得自己去找一只了
All right, so I guess we got to find one of our own,
不管它到底是什么
whatever it is.
我知道在哪能找到
I know where we can find one.
1861年3月5日
March 5, 1861.
桑赖斯 怀俄明州
Sunrise, Wyoming.
咱穿越过去搞定他 就像「星际迷航四」
We'll "Star trek iv" this bitch.
我只看过「深空九号」
I only watched "Deep space nine."
我好像都不认识你们了
It's like I don't even know you guys anymore.
「星际迷航四」 拯救鲸鱼
"Star trek iv." Save the whales.
我们回到过去 去找萨穆埃尔·科尔特
We hop back in time, we join up with Samuel Colt,
捕杀那只凤凰
we hunt the phoenix,
然后带着那些灰烬回来
and then we haul the ashes back home with us.
- 时间旅行吗 - 对
- Time travel? - Yeah.
这计划靠谱么
That's a reasonable plan?
有个家伙能办到
We got a guy who can swing it.
卡西迪奥
Castiel.
现在世界命运悬于一线
The, uh, fate of the world is in the balance.
所以 现身吧
So, come on down here.
来吧 小卡
Come on, Cass,
你家小哥召唤你呢 赶紧下来
"I dream of Jeannie" your ass down here pronto.
求你了
Please.
珍妮
Jeannie?
是瑞秋
Rachel.
我知道你们需要一些帮助
I understand you need some assistance?
有什么我能帮的
How can I help you?
其实我们是想和老大谈一谈
Well, uh, we kind of need to talk to the big kahuna.
我是代表卡西迪奥来的
I'm here on Castiel's behalf.
他在哪
Where is he?
忙着呢
Busy.
- 忙着呢 - 是的
- Busy? - Yes.
我们有一条关于
Well, we've got a line.
该死的万物之母的线索 所以
on the mother of freaking everything, so …
我确信你们的事情很重要
I'm sure your issue's very important.
但卡西迪奥正在统率军队 所以
But Castiel is currently commanding an army, so …
所以我们得跟他的秘书在这儿耗着
So we get stuck with miss money penny.
所以你们要有自知之明
So you need to learn your place.
听着 我不管你是谁
Look, I don't know who you think you are …
我是他的朋友
I'm his friend.
怎么 那你觉得我们不算吗
What, you think we're not?
我觉得你们只是在需要的时候才召唤他
I think you call him when you need something.
我们是在战斗
We're fighting a war.
我们知道
We get that.
很明显你们不知道 否则你们不会
Clearly you don't, or you wouldn't call him.
每次遇到点破事儿就召唤他
every time you stub your toe,
你们这些渺小的…
you petty, entitled little pie…
瑞秋
Rachel.
够了
That's enough.
我说了我会搞定这个
I told you I'd take care of this.
没关系 你可以走了
It's all right. You can go.
- 你要留下 - 你走吧
- You're staying? - Go.
事情办完我就回去
I'll come when I can.
你朋友
Friend of yours?
是的 她是 我的副官
Yes. She's, uh, my lieutenant.
她 很尽责
She's… committed to the cause.
言归正传 你们有什么需要
Now, what do you need?
迪恩哪去了
Where the hell's Dean?
他说要置办补给 我不清楚
Supply run, he said. I don't know.
关于你们的计划
Um, about your plan.
你们只有24个小时
You'll only have 24 hours.
等下 什么
Wait, what?
为什么
Why?
关于你这个问题
Well, the answer to your question.
最好是用一系列偏微分方程式来解释
can best be expressed as a series of partial differential equations.
行了 说简单点
Yeah, aim lower.
我送你们穿越的越远
The further back I send you,
就越难带你们回来
the harder it becomes to retrieve you.
24小时已经是极限
24 hours is all I can risk.
如果我没有在此期限内带你们回来
If I don't pull you home within that time,
我就找不到你们了
You'll be lost to me.
那我们最好给你弄一块手表
Well, then we better get you a watch.
你弄了一堆啥玩意儿
What the hell's all that?
我们要入乡随俗
We are going native.
混入当地人中
Got to blend in.
不用了 谢谢
uh, no, thanks. I'm fine.
- 萨姆 - 迪恩 我穿我这套就行了
- Sam. - Dean, I can … I can wear this.
你想看起来像个太空人么
And look like a spaceman?
听着 就因为你是个
Look, just because you're.
西部牛仔控
obsessed with all that wild west stuff …
- 才没有 - 你超迷的
- No, I'm not. - You have a fetish.
闭嘴 我只是喜欢老电影
Shut up. I like old movies.
你能把克林特·伊斯特伍德的
You can recite every Clint Eastwood movie.
所有电影和台词都倒背如流
ever made, line for line.
包括那些猴子的电影
Even the monkey movies?
对 尤其是那些
Yeah. Especially the monkey movie.
人家叫克莱德
His name is Clyde.
起码把衬衫穿上吧
At least wear the damn shirt.
迪恩 这太二了
Dean, this is stupid.
我看起来太二了
I look stupid.
你俩是要去参加土风舞会吗
You going to a hoedown?
当地的习俗是穿毯子么
Now, is it … is it customary to wear a blanket?
这叫墨西哥范儿斗篷
It's a serape.
没错 这是…
And, yes. It's, uh…
算了不说了 咱们出发吧
Never mind. Let's just go.
这是啥
What's this?
那地方用信用卡可买不到东西
Where you're goin', they don't take plastic.
我会送你们穿越到三月四日
I'll send you back to March 4th.
应该够时间让你们去找科尔特…
That should give you time to find the colt…
以及这个什么凤凰
…and this phoenix creature.
好吧 明天中午见
All right, well, see ya at high noon tomorrow.
伙计
Partner.
（桑赖斯 怀俄明州）
哇哦 要的就是这个
Oh, now we're talking.
我得走了
I have to go.
不是还要把他们带回来么
What about getting the boys back?
24小时之内向我祈祷 我就会回来
Pray for me in 24 hours, and I'll return.
我会为我们所有人祈祷
I'll pray for all of us.
好吧 咱们去找萨穆埃尔·科尔特吧
All right. Let's go find Samuel Colt.
我说 咱应该先去酒吧
Hey, we should try the saloon first,
看能不能从当地人那探到什么消息
Uh, see what we get from the locals.
当然 你说了算 土风哥
Sure. Whatever, sundance.
你觉得我们有时间泡泡酒吧里的妞么
Think we'll have time to hit on saloon girls?
开玩笑的
I'm kidding.
走吧
Come on.
我擦
Oh, damn it.
不是吧
Come on.
知道你踩到什么了吧
You know what that is?
是的 是马的…
Yeah, it's horse …
这叫真实
Authenticity!
今天是1861年3月4日
We stand here today …
我们聚集在这里
March 4th, 1861 …
依法制裁伊莱亚斯·芬奇
to execute justice upon Elias Finch.
因其谋杀了自己的妻子
for the murder of his own wife.
哇 这才叫真实吧
Wow. Talk about authenticity.
由我泰·莫蒂默 现任怀俄明州巡审法官
Sentence handed down by myself,
正式宣布
Tye Mortimer, duly appointed judge of the Wyoming circuit.
你将被处以绞刑
You will be hung by your neck until you die.
你还有什么要说的吗
You got anything to say?
你们会遭到报应的
You're gonna burn for this.
你们所有人
Every one of you.
真欢乐哈
Good times.
话说我们到哪去找萨穆埃尔·科尔特
So where do we find Sammy Colt?
不知道
No idea.
不过我知道该找谁打听了
I think I know who to ask, though.
毯子不错
Nice blanket.
治安官
Sheriff?
能跟我们谈谈吗
Can we have a word?
那要看来者何人了
Depends who's askin'.
伊斯特伍德执法官
Marshal Eastwood.
克林特·伊斯特伍德
Clint Eastwood.
这位是沃克
This here is, uh, Walker.
他是德州骑警
He's a Texas Ranger.
两位小哥 有何贵干
So, what can I do for you boys?
我们在找一个男人
Uh, we're looking for a man.
是嘛
I'll bet.
衬衣不错
Nice shirt, there.
我的衬衣怎么了
What's wrong with my shirt?
你身上非常干净
You're very clean.
比看起来脏一些
It's dirtier than it looks.
我们要找萨穆埃尔·科尔特
We need to find Samuel Colt.
你认识他吗
Do you know him?
- 那位造枪高手 - 是的 他在镇子里吗
- The gun maker? - Yeah. Is he in town?
据我所知 不在
Not that I know of.
你可以去问问酒吧里的埃尔金斯
Might try asking Elkins over at the saloon.
他可是这儿的元老
Been here longer than god.
失了个望
This is not awesome.
你好
Hi.
两位喝点什么
What'll you have?
好 很好 喝点
Oh, uh, okay. Great.
我要你们这里最好的威士忌
I'll have your top-shelf whiskey.
只有一层
Only have the one shelf.
那也不错
That'll do just fine.
给他来点菝葜啤酒
And he'll have a sarsaparilla.
你是埃尔金斯吗
You Elkins?
除了我没别人
One and only.
你认识萨穆埃尔·科尔特吗
You know a man named Samuel Colt?
四年前 他曾经过这里
He passed through here about four years ago.
他还在这儿吗
He still around?
据说 他正在二十英里外的驿站旁边
Rumor is, he's building a railroad stop.
建造一个火车车站
20 miles out of town, just by the postal road.
鸟不拉屎的鬼地方
Middle of nowhere.
恶魔之门
The devil's gate?
地点符合
Location fits.
帅哥们好啊
Howdy, boys.
达拉是我这里的头牌
Darla's my best girl.
和姐玩玩吗
Try me.
想要姐的香吻吗
You want a kiss?
比我想象中脏多了
S-so much more germier than I pictured.
达拉
Darla!
法官大人
Judge.
很高兴见到你
Nice to see you.
我们好像有约吧
I thought we had a date.
哥差一点就贞洁不保了
Wow, that was a close one.
当法官的好处挺多嘛
I guess it's good to be judge.
是啊
Yeah.
喝起来像汽油 我擦
Ohh. It's like gasoline.
菝葜啤酒还不错
Sarsaparilla ain't half bad.
- 治安官 你没事吧 - 没事
- You okay, sheriff? - 'Course I'm okay.
那是鬼
It was a ghost!
不是鬼
It wasn't a ghost.
鬼会留下脚印吗
Unless ghosts leave footprints.
我告诉你 刚刚那是伊莱亚斯·芬奇
I am telling you, Elias Finch was here.
他杀了法官之后
He did…that,
走出了那扇大门
and then he walked out that door.
绞刑没有绞死他
Rope didn't kill him.
以前也有过这种情况
Seen it before.
你知道他可能会在哪里吗
Well, you got any idea where he could be?
可能在很多地方
Could be a thousand places.
你有办法引蛇出洞吗
Well, you got a way to flush him out?
当然 我们会组一队人
'Course. We're gonna form a posse.
然后把芬奇吊起来
Then we're gonna string Finch up right.
再给他头上来一枪
Put a bullet in his head for good measure.
这计划听起来不错
That actually sounds like a good plan.
你们也应该一起来
You two should come along.
天亮后 楼下见
Meet downstairs at dawn.
好的 不见不散
Yeah, we'll be there.
你俩先弄身像样的行头吧
Get yourselves some real gear first, huh?
我觉得 我们应该留心一下芬奇
Well, I think we ought to pay our respects to Finch.
我也这么想
I was thinking the same thing.
你和我想的一样吗
You thinking what I'm thinking?
凤凰涅槃 焚烧猎物
Rose from the ashes, burned up its victim?
我们要找的 有可能不是什么火鸟
You know, maybe we're not looking for a flaming bird.
也许凤凰是人的样子
Maybe the phoenix is actually walking around in cowboy boots.
有点道理 对吧
That makes sense, right?
有可能就是芬奇
Could be Finch.
问题是 我们怎么解决它
So, question is, how do we put this thing out?
我们知道
Well, we do know one thing.
有一样东西可以杀死一切生物
That'll kill friggin' anything, right?
对 科尔特
Yeah, The Colt.
那你去找枪吧
So, you go get the gun.
根据萨穆埃尔·科尔特的日记
But isn't the gun coming here?
枪应该出现在这里啊
I mean, according to Samuel CoIt's journal?
但是这里的人好像都不认识科尔特
Yeah, but people here barely even know who Colt is.
要不你去找到他 然后创造历史
Maybe you got to go find him and make history.
我留下来 和那队人一起
I'll stay here, hook up with the posse.
你懂我的
'cause you know me …
我是治安队磁体
I'm a posse magnet.
我是说 我喜欢《治安维持队》
I mean, I love posse.
还能印在T恤上
Make that into a t-shirt.
你有完没完
You done?
问题是 科尔特在镇外二十英里
Look, the problem is, coIt's 20 miles outside of town.
我去找他 怎么可能在中午前回来
How am I supposed to get there and back before noon?
牛仔 骑马吧
Ride 'em, cowboy.
从另一边上
Wh… uh, try … try the other side.
- 好孩子 - 好吧
- Yeah, good boy. - Right. Yeah. Right.
感觉还不错
This actually feels all right.
好的 放轻松 别紧张
All right, take it … just take it easy.
没事 我很好
Yeah, you bet. I'm good.
- 好的 上午十一点吧 - 别迟到
- All right, 11:00 a.M., right? - Don't be late!
好的 好的
Okay. All right.
走吧 走吧
Go on. Go.
驾
Hyah!
我没事
I'm okay!
可怜的马儿
That poor horse.
请原谅我 对不起
Forgive me! I'm sorry!
自作孽不可活
You had your chance.
跟法官说去吧
Tell it to the judge.
我想跟你谈谈
We need to talk.
是你把我召唤过来的吗
You summoned me here?
卡西迪奥 我最近听说了一些事情
Castiel, I've been hearing things.
一些我不愿相信的事情
Things I don't want to believe.
告诉我那是不是真的
Just tell me if it's true.
什么事
If what's true?
你知道的
You know.
你的邪恶小秘密
Your dirty little secret.
我必须打败拉斐尔
I have to defeat Raphael.
- 你的方式不对 卡西迪奥 - 瑞秋
- Not this way, Castiel. - Rachel.
我们把希望寄托在你的身上…
We put our faith in you, and…
…你却变成了这副模样
…look what you're turning into.
我别无选择
I don't have a choice.
那就别怪我不客气了
Then neither do I.
对不起
I'm sorry.
搞什么飞机…
What the hell…
小卡
Cass?
我们在应战还是撤退
Are we running or fighting?
我们在…
We're…
妈的
Balls.
新帽子啊
New hat.
哥就是帅
I look good.
治安队呢
Where's the posse?
一定是我来早了
I must be early.
或者说只有你一个新手蠢到这种程度
Or you're the only greenhorn dumb enough.
竟然想去捉鬼
to go chasing after a ghost.
你说什么呢
What are you talking about?
治安官可是硬汉 他会过来的
Sheriff's tough as nails. He'll be here.
天啊 治安官死了
Oh, god! The sheriff's dead!
前言撤回
Or not.
这下可好
Great.
如今谁来当治安官呢
Who's the sheriff now?
你要干嘛…
What. What…
现在…
Now…
恭喜你荣升治安官
Congratulations, sheriff.
你是萨穆埃尔·科尔特吗
Samuel Colt?
先生们 找错醉鬼了
You have the wrong drunk, gentlemen.
祝您有美好的一天
Have a nice day.
科尔特 我们一直在找你
We've been looking for you, Colt.
「我们」是指谁
And who might "we" be?
听着…
Listen…
我很久之前就退出江湖了
I've long since hung it up.
我这把老骨头累了 力不从心了
I'm tired, and I'm too damn old for this,
而且毫无疑问的是我不想自找麻烦
and I'm sure as hell not looking for any trouble.
但麻烦还是找上门来了
Well, it's found you anyway.
科尔特 我们知道是你建造了那扇恶魔之门
We know you built that devil's gate, Colt.
所以你要亲手为我们开启
So you're gonna open it for us.
也就是说 要想活命 你别无选择
That is, if you fancy keeping your lungs in your chest.
先生们 快走吧
Walk away, gentlemen.
我们更想把你撕成碎片 你这个软…
Well, I think we'd rather rip you to ribbons, you soft…
真可惜
Ah, that's a shame.
真他妈可惜
A damn shame.
谁啊
Who's there?
蒙戈的糖果快递哟（《神枪小子》中的台词）
Candygram for mongo.
香客 您好
Howdy, pilgrim.
我不是香客
I ain't no pilgrim.
好了 往后退
All right, back up.
你就是这么…
Is that any way to, uh…
问候你的新长官的吗
greet your new boss?
你今早没去参加治安队啊
Missed you at the posse this morning.
就因为你 我只能孤军奋战
I was a one-man wolf pack, thanks to you.
你要到哪里去
What's going on here?
去探望我姐姐
Going to visit my sister.
- 让她先等等吧 - 但如果我…
- Well, she'll have to wait. - But if I don't…
芬奇说他回来是为了向前任治安官…
Finch said he was coming back for the former sheriff…
…莫蒂默法官…
…Judge Mortimer…
…和你索命
…And you.
两人已死 一人苟活
That's two down and one to go.
那就放我走吧
Then just let me go!
你当真以为你能逃出他的魔爪吗
You really think you can outrun him?
他会把你杀掉的
He is going to kill you.
除非…
Unless…
除非怎样
Unless what?
除非我们先搞定他
Unless we gank him first.
「搞定」 什么叫「搞定」
"Gank"? What's "gank"?
长官 你一定是疯了
Mister, you're crazy.
我不干 你自己去吧
No way. You're on your own.
我不是叫你与他同归于尽
I'm not asking you to throw down with him.
我是要求你扮演好你的角色
I'm asking you to play your part.
- 我的角色 - 是的
- My part? - Yeah.
诱饵
Bait.
有人吗
Hello?
我不是恶魔 我不是恶魔
Okay, not a demon! Not a demon!
只是…只是个猎魔人
Just…just a hunter.
你是什么
You're what?
你是萨穆埃尔·科尔特吗
You Samuel Colt?
我叫萨姆·温彻斯特
My name is Sam Winchester.
我…我是来自2011年的一名猎魔人
I'm… I'm a hunter from the year 2011.
证明一下
Prove it.
好吧
All right.
A-all right?
你这就相信我了吗
That's…uh, that's it?
等你入行时间像我一样久的时候…
Well, when you've done this job as long as I have…
…即使是遇到拿着魔砖的未来巨人
…a giant from the future with some magic brick.
也可以微微一笑 绝对不抽
doesn't exactly give you the vapors.
我需要你帮我杀死一只凤凰
I need your help killing a phoenix.
凤凰真的存在吗
A phoenix? They exist?
三小时之后 你将亲手射杀一只凤凰
Well, you shoot one in about three hours.
随你怎么说
If you say so.
这不是我说的
I don't.
而是你自己
You do.
那是…
That's…
我不是太糊涂就是太清醒
I'm either too drunk or not drunk enough.
那我具体要做些什么
So what is it I'm about to exactly do?
凤凰现在在桑赖斯
Well, the phoenix is in Sunrise,
我们现在出发的话 可以…
So, uh, if we leave now, you can…
你的处境我十分理解
I appreciate your situation,
可我帮不了你
but I'm not gonna be of any help to you.
我还有事
I'm booked.
但你明明在这里写着…
Right, but… but you say right here…
白纸黑字也不见得是事实
Don't believe everything that you read.
可你是猎魔人
But you're a hunter.
我退休了
Retired.
- 猎魔人不退休 - 我退出了
- There's no such thing. - I'm out.
猎魔根本没有退出这么一说
There is no getting out.
要知道 在我的时代你可是个英雄
For what it's worth, in my time, you're a hero.
- 我吗 - 没错
- Me? - Yes, sir.
听我说 我们必须杀死这只凤凰
Now, look, we… we need to kill this phoenix.
它的灰烬是杀死
Its ashes are the only thing.
我要对付的怪物的唯一方法
that can kill the monster I'm hunting.
你就先把这烂摊子收收好 然后跟我走
So stow your crap for a few hours, and let's go.
必须马上出发
We got to go now.
你要么跟我走一趟 要么把枪借我
So, either you're coming with me, or I need the gun.
什么枪
What gun?
那把枪
The gun.
那把枪啊
Oh, that gun.
玩牌输了
I lost it in a game of stud.
你撒谎
You're lying.
我有吗
Am I?
我像是说谎的人吗
Now, that doesn't sound like me.
不到一小时前 你打死了两个恶魔
You shot a couple of demons with it less than an hour ago.
你怎么知道的
How do you figure?
两对靴子印
Two pairs of bootprints.
屋里有硫磺味道
Cabin reeks of sulfur.
不赖嘛
Not bad.
你不想要这枪的
You don't want it.
它是一个诅咒 相信我
It's a curse. Believe me.
那好 让我卸掉你的负担
Great. Then let me take it off your hands.
你还是多历练历练 再回来跟我说吧
You go put on a few more miles and come back, and we'll talk.
相信我 我经过的试炼数不胜数
Trust me, I've got plenty of mileage.
信我的话 我是在帮你
I'm doing you a favor. Believe me.
这算什么
So, what?
你能坐视不管吗
You can really just sit there?
我的一生都耗在了猎魔上
I've given my whole life to this.
我受够了
I'm done.
无论怎样你都无所谓吗
So it doesn't matter what happens now.
无所谓
No, it doesn't.
那么你所做的一切 都是无意义的吗
So everything you did, it all means nothing?
把枪给我
Give me the gun.
小卡 怎么弄得像大战变形金刚回来一样
Cass, you… you like you went 12 rounds with truckasaurus.
出什么事了
What happened?
我…
I was, uh…
遭到了背叛
I was betrayed.
瑞秋
Rachel, uh…
拉斐尔
Raphael…
拉斐尔腐化了她 她跑来对付我
He corrupted her. She turned on me.
我很遗憾
Sorry.
那姑娘… 蛮正的
Girl was a real… peach.
她死了
She's… dead.
我受了伤
I… was wounded.
需要安全的环境
I needed… safety.
谢谢你
Thank you.
墙上那手指画做什么的
What's with the finger painting?
那是避开天使监视的符号
It's a warding symbol against angels.
伤得重吗
How bad's it hurt?
我会好起来的
I'll heal.
那就好
Well, good…
现在距离把那两个小子从神奇西部拉回来
'cause we got less than an hour.
只剩不到一小时了
before you pick up the kids at frontierland.
我不能
I can't.
你说什么
Come again?
打斗
This fight…
耗尽了我的力量
drained me.
要是你不行了
Well, if you're up on blocks,
召唤别的小翅膀来也是一样啊
then call in another halo who can get the job done.
我不能
I can't.
总得有个能给你充电的办法吧
Well, there's got to be something that can juice you up.
咒语啦什么的
A spell… something.
有一种方法或许行得通 可是
There is one thing that might work, but…
极其危险
It's extremely dangerous.
真吓人
Shocker.
快说吧
So, lay it on me.
你的灵魂
It's your soul.
你要我做什么
What do you want me to do?
用灵魂做交易 以吻封缄吗
Make another deal? Seal it with a kiss?
你得让我触碰你的灵魂
I need you to let me touch it.
触碰
Touch it?
人类的灵魂是非常纯粹的能量
The human soul… it's pure… energy.
如果我能从中吸取一些能量
If I can siphon some of that off,
或许就可以把萨姆和迪恩接回来
I-I might be able to bring Sam and Dean back.
那问题在于…
And the catch is…?
这种做法的危险性
Doing this is like…
无异于将手伸进核反应堆
putting your hand in a nuclear reactor.
我需要十二万分小心
I have to do it very gingerly.
不然呢
Or…?
不然你会爆炸
Or you'll explode.
好吧
Well.
你稳当些别出差
Keep both hands on the wheel.
就这么干吧
Let's do this.
萨姆你这死小子一辈子都没迟到过
Never been late in your damn life, Sam,
这会子倒磨蹭起来
and now you're dragging ass.
这就是你的妙计呀
So this is your big plan, huh?
芬奇不来就让我烂在这里吗
Just let me rot in here till Finch comes?
差不多吧
Pretty much.
话说回来 他为什么要杀你
Why's he gunning for you, anyway?
看来你是没看见我们绞死他那幕咯
I guess you missed the part where we hung him?
不 我觉得对芬奇这样的存在来说
No, I'm thinking to a thing like Finch,
那都不叫事儿
that's no big whoop.
他本该一走了之 却又特地回来
He would've just blown town, but he came back.
倒像为报私仇
That seems personal.
跟你说吧
I'll tell you what …
你让我出去 我们谈谈
You let me out of here, and we'll talk.
没门
No can do.
把那牢门打开
Open up that cell.
你自己来开
Open it yourself.
你都能把人脸融掉
You melt people's faces off.
弄坏这么个小门想必是小菜一碟了
I'll bet you got the juice to tear that apart easy, don't you?
莫非你不能
Unless you can't.
就像是他们吊起你的时候
Just like you couldn't break those cuffs.
你没法打开那手铐一样
When they strung you up.
铁铐子
Iron shackles…
铁条子 铁钉子
…Iron bars, iron nail.
看出来了吗
See a pattern?
别愁了 我遇到的大多数生物
Don't worry. Most creatures I meet.
都禁不住铁器
can't get it up for iron.
怪物的公共弱点
It's a common monster problem.
原来你是猎魔人
So you're a hunter.
还是治安官
Slash sheriff.
你知道这混蛋做了什么吗
You know what this son of a bitch did?
说来听听
Do tell.
我娶了一个女人
I was married to a woman.
一个好女人 人类
Good woman … human.
我们住在城外 不生是非
We lived outside of town, didn't bother anyone.
不错 有颗善良之心的怪物
Sure, freak with a heart of gold.
喜欢叫我怪物 请便
You want to call me "Monster, " Fine.
但我们那天只是进城
But all we did was go into town.
我在银行只呆了五分钟
I go into the bank for five minutes.
当我出来时 她不见了
I come out, she's gone.
之后我听到了她的尖叫
And then I heard her scream.
这个人
This…Man.
把她抓到小巷
Had her pinned in the alley.
我去阻止他 他掏出枪
I go to stop him, he pulls his gun,
向我射击 然后是她
Shoots me, then her.
她死在了我的怀中
She died in my arms.
可我死不掉
'course, I don't die.
枪声引来治安官
The shots brought the sheriff.
接下来 我就被关入了铁牢
Next thing I know, i'm in iron.
这就是为什么我要他在这里
That's why I want him just where he is …
被困 害怕
trapped, scared.
我把好戏留到了最后
I saved the best for last.
这是真的吗
Is that true?
告诉我
So tell me …
你真的准备以生命
Are you really willing to die.
来保护这个渣滓吗
To protect this piece of filth?
说实话 我一点不关心他
Honestly, I could care less about him.
他是个软弱的混蛋
He's a dick and a coward.
但这不关他的事
But this ain't about him.
我知道你是什么
I know what you are.
真的
Really?
是的
Yeah.
所以 我必须杀了你
So… I got to kill you.
如果你知道我是什么
Well, if you know what I am,
那你就知道你做不到
then you know you can't.
哎哟 我怎么没考虑到这一点
Wow, I should've seen that coming.
迪恩
Dean!
萨姆 快点
Sam, come on, come on!
科尔特呢
Hey, where's colt?
- 来不了了 - 什么
- He's not coming. - What?!
不过他送来这个
But he sent this.
你好啊 美女
Hello, beautiful.
好吧
All right.
来吧
Come on.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
我们可不能让
Well, we can't just.
那些傻瓜陷在那穿不回来 对吧
strand those idjits in deadwood, can we?
可风险…
The risks…
别让我爆炸就行
Just…Don't explode me.
给我出来 芬奇
Get out here, finch!
你干什么
What are you doing?!
来吧 咱单挑
Come on! Let's do this!
这么说 这就是你选择的死法
So, this is how you want to die.
好吧
Fine.
哼哼哈嘿 王八
Yippee-ki-yay, mother…
迪恩
Dean!
灰烬
The ashes!
你得送我们回去
You got to send us back.
迪恩 看看他 他累坏了
Dean, look at him. He's fried.
我再也不想做了
I never want to do that again.
鲍比 你
Bobby, you …
我还活着呢 安妮·奥克利（《狂野西部》中的神枪手）
I'm still kickin', annie oakley.
最起码要恢复个
Be back good as new in…
十到二十年
a decade or two.
我们搞砸了
And we screwed the pooch.
鲍比 对不起
Bobby, I'm sorry.
这里有个叫萨姆·温彻斯特的吗
Is there a sam winchester here?
你是谁
Who's asking?
这事很疯狂
Look, this is nuts …
我和几个人打了赌
Me and a couple guys made a bet.
这东西躺在办公室有
So…This thing's been laying around the office since…
年头了
Ever,
上边有张纸条写这要今天送到这里来
Uh, with a note on it saying to bring it here today.
是萨穆埃尔·科尔特送的
It's from a-a samuel colt?
是的 是的 是我的
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, that's … that's mine.
太棒了 谢谢
Great. Thanks.
好吧
Yeah.
亲爱的萨姆 我在你这个装置上
"Dear Sam, I got this address and date.
找到了这地址和日期
"Off your thingamajig,
我相信附上的东西可能会有用
"And I thought the enclosed might come in handy.
萨穆埃尔·科尔特 敬上
Regards, samuel colt."
这是我想的东西吗
Is that what I think it is?
凤凰的灰烬
Ashes of a phoenix.
你知道这意味着什么吗
You know what this means?
我经受的灵魂汤煮不是毫无意义
Yeah, I didn't get a "Soulonoscopy" For nothing.
是的
Yes.
并且我们要和她开战了
And…It means we take the fight to her.